export let questions = [
  {
    question:
      "Which attribute is used to specify that the script is executed when the page has finished parsing? (only for external scripts)",
    opt1: "parse",
    opt2: "async",
    opt3: "defer",
    opt4: "type",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "The unordered collection of properties, each of which has a name and a value is called _________",
    opt1: "String",
    opt2: "Object",
    opt3: "Serialized Object",
    opt4: "Array",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "The object has three object attributes namely ________",
    opt1: "Class, parameters, object’s extensible flag",
    opt2: "Prototype, class, objects’ parameters",
    opt3: "Prototype, class, object’s extensible flag",
    opt4: "Native object, Classes and Interfaces and Object’s extensible flag",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "To determine whether one object is the prototype of (or is part of the prototype chain of) another object, one should use the ____________",
    opt1: "isPrototypeOf() method",
    opt2: "equals() method",
    opt3: "=== operator",
    opt4: "== opertor",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of a return statement in a function?",
    opt1:
      "Returns the value and continues executing rest of the statements, if any",
    opt2: "Returns the value and stops the program",
    opt3: "Returns the value and stops executing the function",
    opt4: "Stops executing the function and returns the value",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What will happen if a return statement does not have an associated expression?",
    opt1: "It returns the value 0",
    opt2: "It will throw an exception",
    opt3: "It returns the undefined value",
    opt4: "It will throw an error",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      " JavaScript _________ when there is an indefinite or an infinite value during an arithmetic computation.",
    opt1: "Prints an exception error",
    opt2: "Prints an overflow error",
    opt3: "Displays “Infinity”",
    opt4: "Prints the value as such",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "The primary purpose of the array map() function is that it __________",
    opt1: "maps the elements of another array into itself",
    opt2:
      "passes each element of the array and returns the necessary mapped elements",
    opt3:
      "passes each element of the array on which it is invoked to the function you specify, and returns an array containing the values returned by that function",
    opt4: "pass the elements of the array into another array",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "When a class B can extend another class A, we say that?",
    opt1: "A is the superclass and B is the subclass",
    opt2: "B is the superclass and A is the subclass",
    opt3: "Both A and B are the superclass",
    opt4: "Both A and B are the subclass",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "The method that can be used to create new properties and also to modify the attributes of existing properties is _________",
    opt1: "Object.defineProperty()",
    opt2: "Object.defineProperties()",
    opt3: "Both Object.defineProperty() and Object.defineProperties()",
    opt4: "Object.inherit()",
    answer: 3,
  },
];
